<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<openerp>
	<data>
		<template id="report_job_letter_document">
			<t t-call="report.html_container">
				<t t-foreach="get_data_job().get('wiz_bro_rec')" t-as="o">
					<div class="page">
                        <t t-if="get_data_job().get('print_header')">
							<template id="external_layout_header">
								<div class="header">
									<div class="row">
										<div class="col-xs-3">
											<img src="/hr_report/static/src/img/pic.png" />
										</div>
										<div class="col-xs-9 text-right" style="margin-top:10px;"> SENSING YOUR NEEDS</div>
										<div class="row zero_min_height">
											<div class="col-xs-12">
												<div style="border-bottom: 1px solid black;">
												</div>
											</div>
										</div>
									</div>
								</div>
							</template>
                        </t>
							<center>
								<strong>
									<u>
										<b style="color:#0099FF;">JOB OFFER LETTER</b>
									</u>
								</strong>
							</center>
							<br />
							<br />
							<p style="font_size=100%">Dear <span t-esc="o.employee.name" />
							</p>
							<p style="font_size=100%">
								<span style="color:#0099FF;">        
                                Browseinfo</span> is pleased to offer you a position as a <b>
									<span t-esc="o.post.name" />
								</b>. We would like to
                                make the following job offer and trust it will meet with your approval.</p>

							<p style="font_size=100%">As a <b>
									<span t-esc="o.post.name" />
								</b>, you will report to<span style="color:#0099FF;">Browseinfo Erp Department</span>. The
                            primary responsibilities for this position include: Openerp framework, designing and
                            development modules, integrations with other different technologies. We would like you to start
                            work on <b>
									<span t-esc="o.joining_date" />
								</b>. Please contact us immediately if you have any issue regarding that. You will be
                            paid monthly basis schedule after you finished your training period. All payments are subject to
                            statutory deductions, in accordance with legislation (i.e., Income tax, CPP, Employment Insurance).</p>

							<p style="font_size=100%">Your position is subject to 180 day probationary period during which your performance and
                            suitability for employment will be evaluated. It is understood that the probationary period is
                            designed to determine your suitability for continued employment by assessing your skills,
                            performance and interpersonal relationships. Employment may be terminated at any time in this
                            probationary period without notice or pay in lieu of such notice. You agree to abide by all current
                            and future policies, rules and procedures established by<span style="color:#0099FF;">Browseinfo</span>. Please feel free to ask for
                            clarification for anything you are not sure of.<span style="color:#0099FF;"> Browseinfo </span> reserves the right to terminate
                            employment of any employee for just cause at any time without notice and without payment in lieu
                            of notice. <span style="color:#0099FF;">Browseinfo</span>  will be entitled to terminate your employment for any reason other than for
                            just cause, upon providing to you such minimum notice as required by Indian Employment Standards
                            Act.</p>

							<p style="font_size=100%">This offer will be interpreted and enforced in accordance with the laws of the Province of India. This
                            document constitutes the whole and entire agreement between yourself and <span style="color:#0099FF;">Browseinfo.</span>
							</p>

							<br>
							</br>
                            Congratulations and welcome to <span style="color:#0099FF;">        
                            Browseinfo!</span>
							<br />
							<br />
							<p style="font_size=100%">Sincerely,</p>
							<br/>
							<span t-esc="o.hr_name.name" />
							<br/>
							<br/><br/><br/>
							<p style="font_size=100%">I accept this offer.</p>


							<br>
							</br>
							<div class="col-ms-12">
								<table style="width:80%">
									<tr>

										<td>
											<div class="col-md-4">
												<div style="border-top: 1px solid black;">Name</div>
											</div>

										</td>
										<td>
										</td>
										<div class="col-md-4">
										</div>
										<td>
											<div class="col-md-4">
												<div style="border-top: 1px solid black;">Date</div>
											</div>

										</td>


									</tr>

								</table>
							</div>
					</div>
                <t t-if="get_data_job().get('print_header')">
					<template id="external_layout_footer">
						<div class="footer">
							<div style="border-top: 1px solid black;">
								<ul class="list-inline">
									<li>2015 BrowseInfo all rights reserved. <u style="color:#0099FF;">BrowseInfo</u>
									</li>
									<li class="col-xs-12 text-right" style="color:#0099FF;">
										<u>www.browseinfo.in  </u>
									</li>
								</ul>
							</div>
						</div>
					</template>
                </t>
				</t>
			</t>
		</template>

	</data>
</openerp>
